#### Contact

adityagadre2001@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aditya-gadreab08a516a (LinkedIn) sites.google.com/view/ adityagadreconnect/home (Personal)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language) C++

JavaScript

#### Certifications

Python (Basic)

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)
Introduction to Calculus

Introduction to HTML5
JavaScript(Basic)

# Aditya Gadre

Web Development Intern at Newton's Apple | Founder and Developer CoderZDevs Group | International Rated Chess Player | ML Enthusiast | Python Developer Pune

## Summary

Hello Everyone, I am Aditya Gadre.

Coding and developing algorithms on basis of a well analyzed logic is by passion.

I aim to be a Full Stack Developer. I have done 10+ python projects using GUI. Much interested in Software development I aspire to innovate a software for public help and ease away much of complicated software tasks of present decade. I am also a international rated chess player currently competing for a title and have played many inter districts and intercollege level tournaments in my chess career. My chess achievements also include some international as well as national tournament experience with some of most well known Grandmasters of India. Apart from Web and Python based learning my interest also settles in machine learning and learning different programming languages based on the most advanced concepts and syntaxes of OOP's (Object Oriented Programming Languages).

## Experience

Newton's Apple
Web Development Intern
August 2021 - Present (5 months)

PVG's Chess Team Head November 2021 - Present (2 months)

CoderZDevs Group
Founding Member and Developer
June 2021 - Present (7 months)

Develop simple handy and useful project to get along easily with concepts and programming skills efficiently.

#### LetsGrowMore

Web Development Intern November 2021 - December 2021 (2 months)

Successfully Completed two Tasks in Web Development (Basic + Intermediate). Developed a Simple Website for Task Manager and a React App to fetch data from URL. Also during the process of learning and exploring developed a react app for calculator !!! Great Experience and Good Management !!!

Aditya Gadre Chess Academy Coach and Founder April 2020 - December 2020 (9 months)

Hosted several online chess tournaments and provided online chess books thereby encouraging chess amongst many.

Verzeo Student Intern January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)

## Education

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering · (August 2019 - 2023)

G.R Patil College of Arts, Science and Commerce, Dombivli 12th, HSC · (May 2017 - May 2019)

Omkar International School 10th, ICSE · (2007 - 2017)